이건 레어, 이건 미디엄이야
얼른 가!
This one's rare.
This one's medium-well. Go!
안녕, 피비! 식사 어땠어?!
Hey, Phoebe! How was dinner?!
맛있었어! 그냥 인사하러 왔어!
이제 갈게!
Dinner was good! Just saying hi!
Now I'm gonna go!
- 어머, 안녕하세요
- 안녕하세요
-Well, hello there.
-Hi.
이 남자는 메뉴에 없던데
I didn't see this on the menu.
팀, 여긴 피비야
피비, 내 수셰프 팀이야
Tim, this is Phoebe.
Phoebe, this is Tim, my new sous chef.
- 그럼 모니카의 상관?
- 모니카가 상관이죠
-So you're Monica's boss?
-No, she's my boss.
- "수"는 불어로 "아래"거든요
- 그래요
-"Sous" is French for "under."
-I "sous-stand."
팀, 오징어랑 시저 샐러드가 필요해
그리고 페스토 좀 줄래?
Tim, I need a calamari and a caesar salad.
And could you get me the pesto?
- 페스토를 만드셨어요?
- 네
-You made pesto?
-Yes, I did.
당신이 만든 페스토는
"베스트-오"일까요?
Would you say your pesto
is the best-o?
모르겠네요
"꽤 괜찮네-오"쯤 되겠죠
I don't know.
I would say it's pretty good-o.
오징어랑 샐러드도 달라고
I still need the calamari and salad.
목걸이 예쁜데요
I like your necklace.
"네, 모니카, 당신 명령 안 따르면
모두 엉망이 되겠죠"
"Coming up, Monica. I have to obey you,
otherwise the system breaks down."
"나도 알아요"
"그럼 왜 이러고 있는 거야?"
"l know that." "Then why are
we having this conversation? "
- 내가 만든 거예요
- 손재주가 좋네요
-I made it myself.
-You are so talented.
페스토만 하겠어요
Well, it's no pesto.
거두절미하고, 너도 싱글이고
팀도 싱글이야
Let's just cut to the chase.
You're single. You're single.
팀은 11시에 퇴근이고
피비가 전화 기다릴 거야
He gets off work at 11.
She'll be waiting for your call.
내가 네 전화번호 알려줄 테니
오징어하고 샐러드 좀 해줘!
I'll give him your number if I could just
get one calamari and one caesar salad!
나 소리 안 질렀어
벌금 1달러 안 낼 거야
I did not yell.
I am not putting a dollar in the jar.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'레이첼의 데이트'
- 와우, 빙 군! 늦게까지 일하는데
- 제가 그렇죠, 뭐
-Wow, Bing! Burning the midnight oil.
-You know me, sir.
사내 컴퓨터 네트워크를
피해 가는 방법 없나요?
Do you know how I can get around
the office computer network..
쌈박한 포르노 사이트 좀
들어가 보게요
so I can access
the really good Internet porn?
농담도 잘 하는군, 빙 군
You're a joker, Bing.
그게 뭐가 웃기다는 거지?
What's funny about that?
- 미안, 많이 기다렸지
- 괜찮아, 어디 갈래?
-Sorry I kept you waiting so long.
-That's okay. Where do you wanna go?
어디 가고 싶은지 알잖아
I think you know where I wanna go.
- 하드 록 카페?
- 그래
-The Hard Rock Cafe?
-Yeah.
- 또?
- 그래
-Again?
-Yeah.
- 진짜야, 음식이 맛있다니까
- 넌 퍼플 레인 전시가 좋은 거잖아
-I'm telling you, I like the food.
-You like the Purple Rain display.
- 안녕, 밥
- 안녕, 토비, 잘 가
-Hey, Bob.
-Hey, Toby. Have a good night.
- 저 사람 지금 널 토비라고 했어?
- 응, 그게 내 이름인줄 알아
-Did that guy just call you Toby?
-Yeah, he thinks that's my name.
- 왜 제대로 안 가르쳐줘?
- 너무 오랫동안 그렇게 불러서
-Why don't you correct him?
-It's been going on way too long now.
처음 봤을 땐 그냥 지나치던 거여서
아무 말 안 했어
The first time, we were just passing
each other, so I didn't say anything.
두 번째 봤을 때 "토비, 도너츠
먹을래?" 하더라고
The next time he said,
"Toby, want a doughnut?"
그런데 도너츠가 먹고 싶었거든
I wanted the doughnut.
5년이 지나 도너츠는 사라졌고
난 아직 토비야
Five years later, the doughnut's gone
and I'm still Toby.
- 챈들러, 말해줘야 돼
- 너무 어색할 거야
-Chandler, you have to tell him.
-That would be so awkward.
같이 일하는 것도 아냐
저 사람은 6층에 있어
We don't work together.
He's on the sixth floor.
어쩌다 한번 토비라고
하는 게 뭐 어때
So he calls me Toby once in a while.
뮤리엘이라고 부른 것도 아니고
It's not like he's calling me Muriel.
뮤리엘...
왜 뮤리엘이라고 부른다는 거야?
Muriel.
Why would he call you Muriel?
이런, 맙소사
Oh, my God.
챈들러 "M." 빙...
Chandler "M." Bing.
그냥 "M"이 아니었군
너 가운데 이름 뮤리엘이지!
It's not just an "M."
Your middle name is Muriel!
가족끼리 쓰는 이름이야
It is a family name.
챈들러 뮤리엘 빙이라
Chandler Muriel Bing.
네 부모님도 널 참 싫어하셨나보다
안 그래?
Your parents never even
gave you a chance, did they?
드레이크, 자네의 기억상실증의
원인을 알았어
Drake, I've discovered the reason
for your memory loss.
그게 뭐지?
What is it?
두뇌 이식 수술이 실패한 거야
Your brain transplant
wasn't successful.
자네의 몸이 제시카의 두뇌를
거부하고 있다고
Your body's rejecting Jessica's brain.
심각한 건가?
Is it serious?
원래의 몸에서 조직을 떼어다가
Not if we extract tissue
from the original body..
항체를 인공으로 만들어내면
몸이 두뇌를 거부하지 않게 되지
and synthesize antibodies
to stop you from rejecting the brain.
뭐 간단할 것 같은데
그렇게 하지
That sounds simple enough.
Let's just do that.
그러고 싶지만, 제시카의 시신을
파내려고 갔는데
We would, but when we went
to exhume Jessica's body..
시신이 사라졌어
it was gone.
모두 수고하셨습니다
Very nice, people.
나 옷만 갈아입고, 가자
I'll change and we can go.
- 제시카의 시신은 어떻게 됐어?
- TV에 나오면 봐
-What happened to Jessica's body?
-You'll have to see it on TV.
- 너도 모르지?
- 신경도 안 써
-You don't know, do you?
-Couldn't care less.
- 연기 좋았어
- 너도
-Good scene, man.
-You too.
왜? 넌 안 나왔잖아
What? You weren't in it.
캐쉬, 여긴 내 친구 레이첼이야
레이첼, 캐쉬야
Kash, this is my friend Rachel.
Rachel, Kash.
- 안녕하세요
- 지금까진 왜 안 놀러왔어요?
-Hi.
-Why haven't I seen you here before?
조이가 자기 망신시킨다고 해서요
내가 드라마 광인 줄 알아요
Joey just thinks I'll embarrass him.
He thinks I'm a soap opera nut.
물론, 아니죠
Which I'm not.
I'm not.
하지만 당신이 제일 좋아하는
아이스크림이 버터 피칸인 건 알아요
Although, I do know your favorite
ice cream flavor is butter pecan.
개 이름이 월리란 것도 알고
And your dog's name is Wally.
- 어머나, 내가 팔 만지고 있네
- 자, 가자!
-Look, I'm just stroking your arm.
-Here we go.
안녕, 캐쉬, 월리한테 인사 전해줘요
Bye, Kash.
Say hi to Wally.
'센트럴 퍼크'
- 모니카
- 안녕
-Monica.
-Hi.
어젯밤 팀이랑 너무 재밌었어
너무 다정한 남자야
I had the best time
with Tim last night. He is so sweet.
빨리 그 남자의 "수"에
있고 싶네
I can't wait
to get "sous-neath" him.
- 그 사람 해고할 거야
- 왜?
-I have to fire him.
-Why?
형편없어, 꾸물대고
이것저것 태워먹고
He's terrible.
He's slow. He burns things.
내 제빵사도 태워먹을 뻔했다고
He lit my pastry chef on fire.
긴장해서 그랬겠지
네가 좀 무섭긴 해
He was nervous.
You can be intimidating.
나 네 제빵사도 봤는데
좀 혼나도 되겠더라
And your pastry chef can stand
to be taken down a peg.
이젠 눈썹도 없어
혼은 충분히 났지
Well, now she has no eyebrows.
Mission accomplished.
그래도 모니카, 그렇게
일을 좋아하는데
But, Monica, he loves his job so much.
한번만 더 봐주면 안 돼?
제발?
Can't you just give him
another chance, please?
좋아, 하지만 한 사람만
더 태워먹으면 자를 거야
All right. But if he lights
someone else on fire, he's gone.
공평하네, 정말 고마워
That's fair. Thank you so much.
그런데 너도 좀 탔나 보다
Looks like he got you
a little bit too.
이거 돈주고 한 거야
I paid to have this done.
아주 멋진데!
Love it!
있잖아, 캐쉬가 널
정말 좋아한 것 같아
Hey. You know,
Kash really liked you.
네가 매력적이었대
He thought you were charming.
- 난 내가 너무 바보 같았는데
- 동감이야
-I thought I was an idiot.
-I'm with you.
- 자기랑 데이트 해줄 것 같냐더라
- 나 약간 토할 것 같아
-He asked if you'd go out with him.
-I think I'm gonna throw up a little.
- 뭐라고 했어?
- "아니" 했지
-What did you say?
-"No."
뭐야?
What?
넌 임신 중이니까 사람 만나고 싶지
않을 것 같았지
I figured since you're pregnant,
you're not gonna be seeing people.
첫째로, 캐쉬 포드?
그냥 "사람"이 아냐
First of all, Kash Ford?
Not people.
둘째로, 내가 임신했다니까 뭐래?
Did you tell him I was pregnant?
안 했어, 네가 사람들한테 말 안 하길래
그가 '사람'이라고 생각했을때 말야
No. I didn't know if you told people.
This was when Kash was still "people."
- 잘 했어, 나한테 전화하라고 해
- 별로 좋은 생각이...
-Good. Just have him call me.
-I don't think that's..
안 그러면 또 촬영장 구경 가서
배우들 만날 거야
Go do it or I'll come back
to that set. I'll meet more actors.
- 안녕, 밥
- 토비, 오늘 기분 어때?
-Hey, Bob.
-How's my pal Toby doing today?
토비를 만나면 물어볼게
If I see him, I'll ask.
방금 그 친구
6층의 밥 아니었나?
Was that Bob from six
you were just talking to?
- 네
- 자네랑 아나?
-Yeah.
-You know him?
대충 통성명은 한 사이죠
We're on a semi-first-name basis.
- 우리 팀에 데려오는 게 어때?
- 밥을요?
-What about adding him to our team?
-Bob?
여기서 같이 일해요? 매일?
그럴 역량이 있는 친구인지 몰라요
Working here with us? Every day?
I don't know if he has what it takes.
- 6층에선 좋아하던데
- 여긴 11층이잖아요
-They love him down on six.
-But this is 11.
거의 두 배는 더 힘들다고요
It's almost twice as hard up here.
- 알았네, 밥은 그냥 두지
- 그게 좋을 것 같습니다
-Okay, Bob will stay put.
-I think it's best, sir.
사람이 필요하긴 해
처리할 업무가 쌓여간다고
We do need to find somebody.
Work is starting to pile up.
서류 더미가 이만큼 쌓였어
I've got a stack
of documents this high.
그냥 분쇄기에 넣어버리고
받은 적 없다고 잡아떼세요
Just toss them in the shredder
and claim you never got them.
그거 웃긴데, 빙 군
That's a good one, Bing.
왜 내가 하는 말은 심각하게
안 받아들이지?
What does a guy have to do
to be taken seriously around here?
팀에게 기회를 줘봤는데
역시 잘라야겠어
I gave him another chance,
but Tim has got to go.
내게 팀을 추천한
요리사한테 전화했는데
I called the chef
who recommended him to me.
"하하! 속았지!" 그러는 거야!
He said, "Ha, ha! Gotcha!"
- 오늘은 해고하지 마
- 왜?
-But don't fire him today.
-Why?
- 오늘 내가 찰 거란 말야
- 다정하다면서
-Because I'm dumping him today.
-You said he was sweet.
너무 다정해 탈이야
시도 때도 없이 전화해
He's too sweet.
He calls me all the time.
"집에 잘 갔어?
샤워는 잘 했어?"
"Did you get home okay?
Was your shower okay?"
- 전화를 받지 마
- 그럼 집으로 찾아와!
-Don't pick up the phone.
-Then he comes over!
"자기가 걱정되서 왔어"
남자 맞나!
"I was so worried about you."
Be a man!
그럼 자르지 말라고?
So I can't fire him?
여자한테 차인 날에 잘려?
자살해 버릴 걸
And dump him the same day?
He'll kill himself.
내가 해고하고, 넌 1주일만 더 만나
I'll fire him, and you go out
with him another week.
농담하니? 그런 쪼다를 1주 더 보면
내가 자살하겠다
Are you kidding? Another week
with that simp, I'll kill myself.
그냥 오늘 한꺼번에 해
알아서 대처하겠지
We'll both do it today
and he'll just have to deal with it.
알았어, 그런데 누가 먼저 해?
두 번째로 하면 나쁜 년 되는데
Okay. But who's gonna go first?
Whoever goes second is the bitch.
- 뭐?
- 방금 차인 남자를 해고해?
-What?
-Fire a guy that's just been dumped?
나쁜 년이지!
방금 해고된 남자를 차?
Bitch!
And dump a guy that's just been fired?
금발 나쁜 년이지!
Blond bitch!
난 며칠 전부터 해고할 셈이었으니
내가 먼저 통고할게
I wanted to do this days ago,
so I think I should go first.
그래, 그건 말이 된다
All right, that makes sense.
그래도 알게 뭐야!
내가 먼저 할래!
But screw you! I'm going first!
- 토비, 잠깐 볼래?
- 그래, 왜?
-Toby, you got a sec?
-Sure. What's up?
이 쪽으로 옮겨서 일하고 싶었는데
안 될 것 같아
I wanted to get transferred up here,
but it's not gonna happen.
누가 나를 "11층
부적격자"라고 말했대
Apparently somebody thinks
I'm not "11th-floor material."
아니, 챈들러란 자식이
대체 누구야?
Say, who the hell is this Chandler?
오늘밤 술 안 마실 건데
무슨 핑계를 대면 좋을까?
What's the best excuse for why
I'm not drinking on this date tonight?
"난 사실 알콜 중독자였어요"
아니면 "몰몬 교도예요"
"I'm a recovering alcoholic,"
"I'm a Mormon"..
아니면 "어젯밤 너무 많이 마셔서
아직도 좀 취했어요"?
or "I got so hammered last night
I'm still a little drunk"?
임신했다는 말은 안 하고?
You're not gonna
tell him you're pregnant?
아니, 책에서 보니까 세 번째
데이트까지 기다렸다 말하래
I don't think so. Books say wait
till the third date to tell the guy..
뱃속에 새 생명이 자라고 있다고
you got something
growing in your uterus.
- 안녕
- 왔어?
-Hey.
-Hi.
오늘밤 뭐할까?
What do you want to do tonight?
아주 감동적인 우크라이나 영화가
있다던데 관심 있어?
There's a powerful Ukrainian film
playing. Interested?
아니, 하지만 보통 사람들 보는
영화는 같이 볼게
No. But I'll go see
a normal-person movie with you.
- 레이첼, 같이 갈래?
- 못 가, 나 데이트 있어
-Rach, you wanna come?
-I can't. I've got a date.
- 데이트?
- 응, 왜? 이상해?
-A date?
-Yeah. Why, is that weird for you?
아, 아냐, 이상함의 반대지
정상적인 거야
Why, no. It's the opposite of weird.
It's regular.
평범한 일이지
사실 좀 따분하기까지 하네
It's mundane.
It's actually a little dull.
우크라이나 영화 같진 않겠지
It's no Ukrainian film.
아, 귀걸이!
Earrings!
- 데이트를 한다고? 누구랑?
- 내가 동료배우를 소개시켜줬어
-She's got a date? With who?
-I set her up with this actor.
- 네가 소개시켜줬다고?
- 아니
-You set her up?
-No.
- 무슨 생각으로?
- 괜찮다고 생각했지
-What were you thinking?
-That it was okay..
너희들은 데이트 안 한지
5년째잖아
because you two haven't dated
in five years.
내 애가 걱정돼서 그러지, 레이첼이
만나는 남자는 애도 만나는 거야
I'm worried about my baby.
Whoever she dates, my baby dates.
- "배우" 녀석이 어디로 데려간대?
- 야! 나도 역시 "배우"라고
-Where is this "actor" taking them?
-Hey! I'm an "actor" too.
유람선 타고
스테이튼 아일랜드에 간대
They're taking the ferry
to a place on Staten lsland.
내 아이가 유람선을 탄다고?
그게 얼마나 위험한 건지 알아?
My baby's going on a ferry? Do you
have any idea how dangerous those are?
무지 크고 무지 느린 배
얘기하는 거 아냐?
Aren't we talking about
those big boats that go really slow?
차라리 비행기에서 뛰어내리거나
서로 성냥 갖고 놀면서 태우라고 하지?
Why not just jump out of an airplane
or burn each other with matches?
- 안녕, 조이
- 안녕, 캐쉬, 로스, 캐쉬야
-Hey, Joey.
-Hey, Kash. Ross, this is Kash.
오늘밤 유람선 타신다면서요
Hey, I hear you're going
on a ferry tonight.
좀 겁이 없는 분이네요?
Bit of a daredevil, are we?
이거 너무 헤픈 여자 같지 않아?
안녕, 캐쉬
Do you guys think this is too slutty?
Hi, Kash.
- 안녕, 레이첼, 준비됐죠?
- 네, 그럼 나중에 보자
-Hey, Rachel. You ready to go?
-Yeah. See you guys later.
두 사람 재미있게 놀다와
그래, 헤퍼 보인다!
Have a great time, you guys.
And yes, it is too slutty!
안녕
Hi.
전화해줘서 고마워
항상 나만 전화하는 것 같았거든
I'm glad you called.
I feel like I'm always calling you.
무슨 일이야?
피비 다 괜찮은 거야?
What's up?
Is everything okay with Phoebe?
곧 그렇게 될 걸
It will be in a minute.
- 팀, 자긴 참 좋은 사람이야
- 자기랑 함께라서 그래
-Tim, you're a really great guy.
-That's because I'm with you.
그냥 난, 지금은 좀 시기가...
It's just, I'm in a place in my life
right now where..
미안해, "속보입니다"
So sorry. "This just in."
식당이야, 모니카 씨가
당장 오라는데
It's the restaurant.
Monica needs me right away.
아냐! 무슨 속셈인지 알아
그냥 여기 있어
No, she doesn't! I know what that is.
You can stay.
나도 보고 싶을 거야, 피비
I'll miss you too, Pheebs.
여기 널 담아두고 있을게
And I will be holding you right here.
무슨 영화 볼래?
자막 읽어야 하는 건 싫어
What movie do you wanna see?
And not one I have to read.
읽는 건 책으로도 충분해
I get that from books.
- 책?
- 좋아, 자동차 잡지나 시리얼 상자야
-Books?
-Okay, car magazines, cereal boxes..
아무튼 그걸로 충분해!
but it's enough!
영화는 보지 말자
그냥 여기서 이러고 있자고
Let's not see a movie.
We'll just stay here and hang.
- 레이첼 돌아오는 걸 기다리게?
- 뭐, 네가 그러고 싶다면야
-Just wait for Rachel to come back?
-Hey, if that's what you wanna do.
야, 너 왜 그래?
Dude, what is going on?
- 데이트 결과를 알아야 해
- 왜?
-I have to find out how it went.
-Why?
- 내 아이의 계부가 될 수도 있어
- 데이트 한번 했다고 결혼해?
-He could be my baby's stepfather.
-One date and they're getting married?
캐쉬가 너냐?
He's not you!
못 믿겠어, 데이트를 한다니!
I can't believe she's dating!
- 그럼 뭘 어쩔 줄 알았어?
- 몰라
-What did you think she was gonna do?
-I don't know.
- 이렇게 된다니 믿을 수 없군
- 무슨 소리야?
-I can't believe this is happening.
-What do you mean?
또 아이가 생기면
달라질 줄 알았단 말야
I thought when I had another kid,
it'd be different.
벤을 사랑하지만, 캐롤과 수잔네
다시 데려다 줄 때마다
I love Ben. But every time
I drop him off at Carol and Susan's..
마음이 조금씩 아파와
it breaks my heart a little.
내가 항상 그린 그림은
나와 아내가 침대에 누워 있고
I've always had this picture
of me and my next wife in bed..
우리 애가 달려와 침대에서
모두 같이 신문을 보는 거였어
my kid comes running in, leaps up
on the bed and we all read the paper.
어쩌면 과학난을 서로
보겠다고 다툰다던가
Maybe fight over the science section.
- 멋진데, 아직 가질 수 있는 그림이야
- 아니, 레이첼은 남자랑 만나고 있고
-That's nice. You can still have that.
-No. Rachel's out with some guy.
내 아이도 같이 가버렸어
My baby went with her.
그림은 점점 멀어져 가고 있다고
If anything, that picture
keeps moving further away.
뭐 하나 물어봐도 돼?
Hey, can I ask you something?
네가 그린다는 그 그림에서
네 아내가 레이첼이야?
In this picture of you and your wife,
is your wife Rachel?
예전엔 그랬지
It used to be.
이젠 그냥 얼굴 없는 여자야
Now she doesn't really have a face.
그런데 몸매는 죽여
Smokin' body, though.
잘 생각했어, 그런데 로스,
그 얼굴은 레이첼 얼굴이 아니잖아
Good call. But the face, Ross,
the face isn't Rachel.
아니지, 하지만 레이첼이었다면
얼마나 일이 쉽겠어?
No. But how much easier would it be
if it were?
그건 레이첼이 원하는 게 아냐
That's not what she wants.
알아, 나도 억지로 레이첼과
사랑에 빠질 순 없어
I know. And I can't force myself
to fall in love with her.
로스, 새로운 그림을 그려봐
Ross, maybe you need a new picture.
네가 생각한 그림은 아니겠지만
어떻게 되든 간에
It won't be what you thought.
But no matter what..
새로운 아이가 생기는 거야
네 아이가
there's gonna be
a brand-new little baby. Your baby.
그림이야 어떻든 무슨 상관이야?
Who cares what the picture looks like?
그래
Yeah.
우리끼리 나가서
재미있는 거 하고 놀자
Let's you and me go out
and have some fun.
너 하고 싶은 거 하자, 얼른
Whatever you want. Come on.
- 우크라이나 영화 봐도 되지
- 안 돼, 재미있게 놀자니까
-We can catch that Ukrainian film.
-No, I said fun.
- 토비?
- 안녕, 바비
-Hey, Toby?
-Hey, Bobby.
내 이름은 밥이야
It's Bob, actually.
너 여기서 일하지, 챈들러 빙의
사무실이 어디야?
You work up here. Where's
Chandler Bing's office?
그래, 저기 저...
Yeah, it's right..
저쪽이야, 그런데 왜?
Right there.
Let me ask you, why?
그 자식 만나서 뭐가 문젠지
한번 물어보려고
I wanna talk to that bastard,
see what his problem is.
좋아, 밥, 들어봐
Okay, Bob. Listen.
네가 그렇게 된 건 나 때문이야
I'm the reason you didn't get the job.
- 토비, 관둬
- 밥
-Toby, don't.
-Bob.
네가 그자식 대신
뒤집어 쓸 필요 없어
Toby, I'm not gonna let you cover
for him.
네가 뭐라고 해도 챈들러 녀석한테
더 화만 날 뿐이야
Anything you say will just get me
more upset with Chandler.
그럼 내 입장이 아주 곤란해지는데
That puts me
in a difficult position.
네가 챈들러를 상대하면
너도 똑같은 수준이 돼
You do anything to Chandler,
it's gonna bring you down to his level.
그건 그렇지
I guess you're right.
녀석이 우쭐할 짓은 하지마
넌 챈들러보다 나아, 우리 다 그래
Don't give him the satisfaction.
You're better than Chandler. We all are.
특히 나, 토비는 더 그래
Especially me, Toby.
- 다 괜찮은 거예요?
- 글쎄, 봐야 알지
-Is everything okay?
-That depends.
- 피비랑 사이는 어때?
- 좋아요, 우리 소개해줘서 고마워요
-How are you and Phoebe?
-Great. Thanks for introducing us.
천만에, 그래, 안 됐지만
나쁜 소식을 전해야겠어
My pleasure. Okay, I'm afraid
I've got some bad news.
- 피비!
- 모니카!
-Phoebe!
-Monica!
- 넌 해고야!
- 우리 헤어져!
-You're fired!
-I'm breaking up with you!
헤어지자고
I'm breaking up with you.
- 해고됐다고
- 왜요?
-You're fired.
-Why?
미안, 난 지금 누구랑
사귈 준비가 안 됐어
I'm sorry. I'm not ready
for a relationship right now.
나도 미안해, 하지만 난
내 방식대로 일하는 게 좋아
I'm sorry too.
But I like things done a certain way.
- 우린 서로 안 맞아
- 그래, 우리도 그거, 안 맞아
-The chemistry's just not right.
-The chemistry thing for us too.
우와, 알았어요
Wow. Okay.
내가 좀 지나쳤던 건 알아
자기가 너무 좋아서 그랬어
I realize I came on a little strong.
It's because I think you're amazing.
제게 기회를 주셔서
정말 감사했어요
I wanna tell you how much I appreciate
you giving me an opportunity.
당신은 제가 같이 일해본
요리사 중 가장 재능 있어요
You're the most talented chef
I've ever worked for.
아무튼...
Anyway..
- 팀, 잠깐
- 네?
-Tim, wait.
-Yeah?
내가 너무 성급했어, 이런 일은
배우는데 시간이 걸리는 법인데
I spoke too quickly. There's
a learning curve with this job.
다시 한번 일해보자
Maybe we could try it again.
고마워요
저 정말 잘 할 수 있어요
Thank you so much.
I know I can be better.
그럼, 팀...
행운을 빌어
And, Tim, I just want to say
good luck here.
- 안녕
-Hello.
-Hi.
데이트는 어땠어?
How was the date?
혼자서 15달러 어치 초콜릿을
사고 있잖아, 어땠을 것 같아?
I'm alone and I just bought $15 worth
of candy bars. What do you think?
- 어떻게 된 건데?
- 임신 중이라고 얘기했어
-What happened?
-I told him I was pregnant.
- 반응이 안 좋았나 보지?
- 옛날 네 반응 보단 낫더라
-He didn't take it so well?
-Well, better than you.
- 그래도 내가 원한 반응은 아냐
- 그래?
-But still not what you want.
-Oh?
묘한 모습으로 더듬거리고 그러더니
Yeah. He got all weird and sputtery.
Then he said:
"치질이 문제라면서요"
그러더라
"I hear those hemorrhoids
are a bitch."
- 좋은 남자 같네
- 그러게 말야
-He sounds swell.
-Doesn't he?
기분 좀 낫게 해줄까?
앉아봐
You want a little cheering up?
Sit down.
누구 가운데 이름이 뮤리엘이게?
Guess whose middle name is Muriel.
챈들러 M. 빙
어머나, 세상에
Chandler M. Bing.
Oh, my God.
- 데이트 망쳐서 안 됐다
- 괜찮아
-I'm sorry about your date.
-It's all right.
데이트니 뭐니 이젠
그만둘 때인가봐
I guess I'm just done
with the dating thing.
내 삶에 찾아온
또다른 변화일 뿐이지
Just one more thing in my life
that's completely different.
- 정말 힘들어
- 그래, 알아
-This is hard.
-Yeah, I know.
하지만 7개월만 참으면
네가 지금껏 사귄 어느 남자보다도
On the other hand, in seven months
you're gonna have something..
더 사랑하게 될 존재가 생기는 거야
that you're gonna love more than
any guy you've ever gone out with.
기다려 보라고
Just wait.
네 아기가 처음으로 네 손가락을
쥘 때까지 기다려봐
Wait until the first time
your baby grabs your finger.
상상도 못할 거야
You have no idea.
고마워
Thanks, sweetie.
- 커피 마시러 갈래?
- 아냐, 가서 초콜릿 열 개쯤 먹을래
-You wanna grab some coffee?
-No. I'm gonna go eat 10 candy bars.
- 기분 나아진 줄 알았는데
- 나아진 거야, 20개 샀거든
-I thought I cheered you up.
-You did. There are 20 in here.
- 잘 가
-Good night.
로스? 나 모나예요
결혼식에서 봤죠
Ross? Hey, it's Mona.
From the wedding.
- 아, 안녕하세요!
- 안녕
-Oh, hi!
-Hi.
- 어떻게 지내요?
- 좋아요, 아직 나한테 춤 빚졌는데
-How are you?
-I'm good, except you owe me a dance.
그렇죠, 혹시 우크라이나 영화
안 보고 싶으세요?
That's right. Well, would you be
interested in seeing a Ukrainian film?
어머, 진심이시구나, 그래요
Oh, you're serious. Sure.
그래요, 그럼...
Great. Well..
- 커피 한잔 더 해야겠어요
- 네, 내가 갖다줄게요
-I think I need another cup of coffee.
-Sure, let me get it for you.
'리처드 L. 콕스 시니어를 추모하며'
밥?
Bob?
밥!
Bob!
- 뭐하는 짓이야?
- 여기가 챈들러 사무실이래
-What the hell are you doing?
-This is Chandler's office.
얼른, 토비, 좀 도와줘!
Come on, Toby. Give me a hand!